现在风速已达到60英里每小时
With winds in the 60-mile-per-hour range,
我们再次提醒大家要呆在屋里
we, once again, recommend everyone stay indoors...
电力公司的工人被雷电击伤
T.X.U. Line worker struck by lightning.
被击飞了50英尺 血压稳定
Knocked him 50 feet. B.P.'s stable,
但他现在已经室性早搏了
but he's having runs of P.V.C.S.
-保罗 你来给我搭把手 -谢谢
- Paul, you're with me. - Thanks.
给他做一个遥测监测
Get him on telemetry,
我需要做一个心电图
and I need a 12-lead EKG, stat.
送他去手术室然后通知血库
Let's get him to the OR and have the blood bank
交叉配6单位A型阳性血
type and cross 6 units of A-positive.
-马上 -我希望闪电不要离这太近
- On it. - I hope it's not close.
天哪 这根之前桑迪飓风似的
Good lord, we got our own Sandy.
这是因为闪电
That's from lightning?
闪电的电流破坏了毛细血管
Broken capillaries cause by lighting current,
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
会持续好几天
can last a couple of days.
-好的 -由多数病灶引起的室性早搏
- Okay. - Multifocal P.V.C.S,
检测肌钙蛋白和细胞角蛋白
add a troponin and a total-C.K.
翻译：壮壮 Windy 濯涟 Bezero Aevus 烈焰鸟 Winni 小泥 呆毛
再来5只倍他乐克
And push 5 of metoprolol.
嗨 克里丝塔 看下这个
Hey, Krista, check this out.
-看见这两个白点了 -恩
- See those two white spots? - Yeah.
这应该就是嵌入他指关节里的两个牙齿了
Those would be teeth embedded in that dude's knuckles.
还有更糟的嘛
Can you top that?
我刚刚从一个家伙的屁股里拔出了一根洋基蜡烛
I just pulled a Yankee candle out of a guy's butt.
校对：小17 濯涟 Bezero miku Vera强妹 VeraS
-你赢了 -克里丝塔
- Uh, you win. - Hey, Krista.
我有张X光片你应该看看
I got an X-ray you should see since you're going into ortho.
-它很有趣 -好的
- It's pretty juicy. - Okay.
我在想我们应该挑一个共同的休息时间
I was thinking we could sync our breaks
然后一起分析它们
and look at them together.
是的 我现在挺忙的
Oh, yeah, I might be kind of busy,
医学顾问：酥酥 慕斯
我忙完再叫你
but I'll let you know.
你不该说话的
You do not say a word.
因为我会吸引呆子
'Cause I'm a nerd magnet.
而且我不想打击他们
And I hate hurting their feelings.
嗨 今天的呆子就是明天的丈夫
Hey, the nerds of today are the husbands of tomorrow.
此外还有四间顶尖水平的创伤病房
In addition to having four state-of-the-art trauma rooms
和一个专业创伤扫描仪
and a dedicated trauma CAT scan machine.
后期：D  时间轴：阿黎
好的 我承认你让我印象深刻
All right, I'll admit I'm impressed.
斯科特医生
Dr. Scott Clemens --
圣安东尼奥创伤部门的头
Head of San Antonio Memorial Trauma Department.
哇 非常棒 你不这么认为吗
Whoo! Has a certain ring to it, don't you think?
总监助理：Bezero  总监：琪琪 络睿
我很欣赏 迈克尔
I appreciate the tour, Michael,
但我仍要仔细想想
but I'm still thinking it over.
这是一个好的选择 我来告诉你
It's a sweet deal, I'm telling you.
并且在达拉斯你得不到这样的机会
And not the kind of opportunity you will get in Dallas.
我要来观察这里的夜班情况几个小时
I came to observe the night shift for a few hours,
但是至于做什么承诺
but as far as making any commitment...
我还有些东西要弄明白
We still have some stuff to figure out.
弄明白什么
What's to figure out?
你们两个也可以终止异地恋了
The two of you can stop this whole long-distance thing,
来吧 生一堆小孩
Get settled in, pop out a couple of monkeys, and boom! Done!
拉戈萨先生 理查斯先生的电话
Mr. Ragosa, Dr. Richards on the phone for you.
不要再纠结了 少年
Don't drag your feet, cowboy.
董事会在等着呢 他们需要一个名字
The board is waiting. They want a name.
-这一点都不尴尬啊 -是啊
- That wasn't awkward. - Yeah.
这对我是很重要的一个决定
Look, this would be a huge move for me.
我不得不确定这是不是我想要的
I have to be sure it's one that I want to make.
但他是对的
But he's right.
-这会让我们生活的更方便了 -是啊
- It would make our lives easier. - It would.
恩 我也不得不确定一下
And, hey, look, I have to be sure, too.
你知道 最后一次我和一个男人住
You know, the last time I lived with a guy...
结果并不好
It didn't work out too well.
但我不是那个男的
But I'm not that guy.
是呀 你不是
No, you are not.
伙计
Hey, guys.
托佛 你怎么样
Hey, Topher, are you okay?
挺好
Yeah.
托佛刚做过外科手术
Topher had surgery recently.
这是第一个回来的夜晚
First night back.
永远不要做那个输精管切除手术 斯科特
Don't ever get a vasectomy, Scott.
没有人应该感受下面的那种痛苦
No man should ever feel this kind of pain down there.
托佛 真为你遗憾
Topher, sorry, man.
看到你我都觉得疼
It hurts just looking at you.
是啊 我能从你的笑声中感觉到
Yeah, I can tell by your laughter.
不是自己的蛋蛋疼总是有趣的
Ball pain is always funny when it's not yours.
今晚放轻松点
Just try to take it easy tonight.
就处理感冒和流感 怎么样
Stick with the colds and flus, okay?
兰德里 你还记得斯科特 对吧
Hey, Landry. You remember Scott, right?
是呀
Yeah.
我听说你要接手了创伤科
I heard you were taking over trauma.
正想着呢
Thinking about it.
哦 那应该会挺有趣的
Oh, that should be interesting.
乔丹告诉我你正和TC谈恋爱呢
So Jordan tells me that you're seeing T.C. Now.
-是吗 -忏悔吧
- Oh, did she? - Repent!
我去
Oh, boy.
我将用愤怒掩盖你们 罪人
For I bring my wrath upon thee, sinners.
末日即将到来
The end is nigh.
莫利 准备精神疾病房间
Molly, prep the rubber room.
忏悔吧
Repent!
电话是今晚主治创伤的医生打的
That was tonight's on-call trauma attending.
他家来着的道路封闭了
Roads are wiped out by his house,
因为道路封闭我们已经有三个护士来不了了
and we're already short three nurses because of the closures.
我们已经受到了暴风雨的很大冲击
We're gonna get slammed by this storm.
伙计们 龙卷风
Hey, guys, the tornado
刚刚摧毁了响尾蛇停车场
just tore through the Sidewinder trailer park.
消防队已经在路上了
The fire department is on the way.
救护人员在路上出了事故
The paramedics got in an accident en route.
我们要去了 TC
Here we go. Okay, T.C.?
给他做个胸腔X光片 我来了 我来了
Take him for a chest X-ray. I-I'm on it. I'm on it.
托佛 伙计 我担心你和你那碎了的扁桃体
Topher, buddy, I'm afraid you and your smushed man tonsils
我只能坐在一边了
are gonna sit this one out.
-再用灵敏测试仪 -你好 让德鲁和你一起 好吗
- Again with the sensitivity. - Hey, take Drew with you, okay?
我可以的 我可以的
I'll do it. I'll do it.
你确定
Are you sure?
过去五年我都做得是搜索和营救工作
I've done search and rescue for the past five years.
除此之外 还有更好的方法获取地形吗
And besides, what better way to get the lay of the land?
我喜欢这种 能做 的态度
I love this can-do attitude!
好的 注意 听好了 各位
Okay! Ho! Listen up, everybody!
克莱门斯医生在这有特权
Dr. Clemens hereby has privileges.
现在从这滚出去
Now get out of here.
跟着我 别挡我的路
Just follow my lead and don't get in my way.
我刚要和你说同样的话
I was gonna say the same to you.
看那
Look at that.
过去和未来就在你眼前
The past and future right before your eyes.
闭嘴 否则我揍你
You shut up, or I'll smack you in your nuts.
我们这有一位32岁带有钝伤的健壮女性
We got a 32-year-old healthy female with blunt trauma.
不知道细节
Don't know the specifics.
在车载设备绑好之前不要让我的人进来
Not sending my men in until the mobile unit's tied down.
你好 我们需要另外五个
Hey! We need another five.
她可能没有另外五个
She might not have another five!
跟好我 在那 我们走
Follow me. Over here. Let's go.
斯科特 过来帮我
Scott! Help me with this.
-我抓住了 -在你的后面
- I got this. - Right behind you.
她在那
There she is.
好的 夫人 我们抓住了
It's okay, ma'am. We got this.
没事了 夫人
It's okay, ma'am.
我们带你从这离开
We're gonna get you out of here.
一切都会好的
It's gonna be okay.
反常的呼吸声
Abnormal breath sounds.
可能是肺功能衰竭
Possibly a collapsed lung.
是的 肺疝
Okay. Pulmonary hernia.
肺看上去严重撞伤 她需要尽快手术
The lung looks severely contused. She needs the OR asap.
-递给我一个AB垫 -我正在准备
- Hand me an A.B. Pad. - I'm on it.
给她上氧气面罩
Get her on an O2 face mask.
向前移动 伙计们
Move it along, guys!
在这可能有另一场悲剧
We're gonna have a second tragedy here.
好的 把救助篮放在这
Well, get the rescue basket over here.
-我们现在要移动她 -一起走 伙计们 到这儿
- We need to move her now! - Let's go, guys! Get in here.
夫人 我们需要你尽可能的保持安静
Ma'am, we need you to stay as still as possible.
我们将带你离开这
We're gonna get you out of here.
夫人 它是什么
Ma'am, what is it?
我儿子厄尼 他在那
My son Ernie. He's over there.
好的 我们必须移动她 现在带她离开这
Okay, we have to move her. Get her out of here now.
好了 我们走 我们走
Okay? Let's go. Let's go.
好的 夫人 我们将带你和你儿子离开这
It's okay, ma'am. We're gonna get you and your son out of here.
-厄尼 -过来 我们需要那个篮子
- Ernie! - Come on! We need that basket.
-厄尼 -救命
- Ernie! - Help.
你好 小伙子 没事了 没事了
Hey, little guy, it's okay. It's okay.
好的 相当简单 保罗
All right, it's pretty simple, Paul.
在钉子底部注射麻药
Inject lidocaine at the base of the nail,
开一个小切口 把它拔出来
make a small incision, and pull it out.
-我来拔 -好的
- I can do that. - All right.
好的 我们带了什么到这
All right. What do we got here?
我试图
I was trying to film the
从前窗拍摄暴风雪 它突然进来了
storm from my front window, and it blew in.
咳 相当严重的撕裂
Whoa, that's a pretty bad laceration.
我们能看见右后方
We can sew that right back up.
-好的 护士 你准备好了吗 -好了
- All right, nurse, you want to prep him? - Yes.
我希望你抓到了一些好镜头
I hope you got some good footage.
拉戈萨先生
Mr. Ragosa.
妈的
Son of a...
夜班医生
第五集
好了 各位 放松点
Okay, everybody, take it easy!
我们的应急发电机将恢复运转
Our emergency generators will come back on
在三 二
in three... two...
看见了
See?
没有什么好担心的 我们有四个备份的小发电机
There's nothing to worry about. We have four backup gennies.
-只有两个 -什么
- Make that two. - What?
预算消减 懂了么
Budget cuts. Got it.
曾经有用电激增的时候
There was an explosion at the power transmission station.
电力煤气说一条明线破裂了
T.X.U. Says an open line got ruptured.
-好吧 还有多久才能来电 -他们没说
- Well, how long until we're back online? - They wouldn't say.
我们有足够的柴油供发电机用
We have enough diesel for the gennies.
我们只需要重新优先排序
We just need to re-prioritize
输电网保证每件事正常运转
the grid flow to keep everything on.
莫利 关闭所有不重要的用电装置
Molly! Turn off all non-essential electronics.
重症监护室得到最大的份额
ICU gets the lion's share of the juice.
请联系下TC和斯科特
And please check on T.C. And Scott.
我们需要他们过来
We need them back here.
好的 我来着手处理
Okay. I'm on it.
她是胸部严重损伤导致的低血压
She's hypotensive with a major chest defect
伴随肺衰竭 通知医院
and a contused lung. Notify the hospital.
我需要一个开放的胸部皮瓣闭合装置
I need a setup for a flap closure of an open chest.
我们走
Let's go!
我们找到了你儿子 他安全了
We got your son. He's gonna be okay.
带他们离开这 我们得走了
Get them out of there now! We gotta go!
走吧 医生 现在
Let's go, doc! Now!
他没事 只是有些擦伤
He's okay. He's barely got a scratch.
你没事了 小男子汉
You're okay, little man.
我曾试着保护我妈妈
I was trying to protect my mommy,
但她让我躲进树篱
but she made me get inside the hedge,
-她挡在我前面 -那就是母亲会做的
- and she got in front of me. - That's what moms do.
我们将住在柳市 那儿有几个背包客
We now go live to Willow City where several hikers...
来自莫利护士
From Nurse Molly --
她侄女的电话 以免你丢了
Her niece's number in case you lost it.
好吧 她已经给过我三次了
Yeah, she's given it to me about three times already.
我用尽了理由
I'm running out of excuses.
告诉她你已经有女朋友了
Tell her you have a girlfriend.
我不能
I can't.
最近的理由是我正在分手
My last excuse was I was getting over a breakup.
她认为我应该重新回到马背上
She thinks I should get back on the horse.
告诉她我是你的新马
So tell her I'm your new horse.
这样她就不会干涉你了
Then she'll leave you alone,
龙和地下城的人们将不再打扰我
and the Dungeons & Dragons crowd will quit bothering me.
我确定你能降住它们当中最厉害的
I'm sure you can buck with the best of 'em,
除了工作
but workplace,
你是一个实习医生 可能看起来不相称
you're an intern, might seem inappropriate.
我不想引人注意
I don't want to draw attention.
你知道 如果你问我 你的妻子应该在这
You know, if you ask me, your wife should be here
推着你的轮椅转转
pushing you around in a wheelchair.
是的 她 她增加了70磅
Yeah, her -- her gaining 70 pounds
葡萄柚大小的痔疮
in hemorrhoids the size of grapefruits
不全是放大她对我的同情
doesn't exactly amp up her sympathy for me.
你好 玛雅
Hey, Maya.
这周那原本可能是快乐的一家
That must have been a happy household this week.
是的 -谢谢你 亲爱的
Yeah, well -- thank you love --
实际上 她和我女儿去了她母亲的
Actually, she and my daughter went to her mother's
让我安静的恢复
to let me recover in peace.
我 我有点像病人一样暴躁
I-I get a little cranky as a patient.
各位 唔 各位知道
You guys, uh... you guys know
我能从哪找到德 拉 克鲁兹医生吗
where I can find Dr. De la Cruz?
但你怎能让我看那
But how about you let me look at that --
不 我 我告诉你 我正在找德 拉 克鲁兹医生
No, I-I told you. I'm looking for Dr. De la Cruz.
嗨 放松点 保罗
Hey, take it easy, pal.
没事的 肯尼
It's okay, Kenny.
为什么 为什么你不霸占兰德里
Why -- why don't you go grab Landry?
并且 唔 可能要警惕那得警棍医生
And, uh, maybe alert Dr. Nightstick over there
-准备好 -抓住你了
- to be ready. - Got you.
因此 因此你 你认识
So -- so you -- you know --
-你认识德 拉克鲁兹医生 -是的 是的
- you know Dr. De la Cruz? - Yes. Yes.
插管陷害我
Set me up for intubation
用一个3MAC和7OET管子 现在
with a Mac 3 and a 7-O E.T. Tube, now!
我们有什么
What do we have?
肺疝
Pulmonary hernia.
你要让她好起来
You have to make her better!
厄尼 厄尼 她会好起来的 我保证
Ernie! Ernie! She's gonna be fine. I promise.
把她准备好 我们需要换衣服
Get her prepped. We have to get changed.
保罗 保罗 来这
Paul! Paul, come here.
这是我们的新朋友 厄尼
This is our new friend Ernie.
好了 我需要你去检查他的切口和刮伤
Okay, I need you to check him for cuts and scrapes
找一位护士照看他
and find a nurse to look after him
当我们照顾他母亲的时候
while we take care of his mother.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好 厄尼 我是保罗
Hey, Ernie. I'm paul.
你好 你很酷 伙计
Hey, you cold, buddy?
好了 走吧
Okay, come on.
我们有什么
What do we got?
脉搏75 收缩压84
Pulse ox 75%. B.P.'s 84 systolic.
她已经上了氧气
She's already on 100% oxygen.
好的 这有个巨大的空气泄露
Okay, there's a huge air leak from
在右边的支气管肺伤口
the bronchopulmonary injury on the right side.
我们需要转移空气流动到左边
We need to divert ventilation to the left side,
否则血压永远都上不来
or her sats won't come up.
心脏收缩率下降到60 脉搏逐渐微弱
Systolic's down to 60. Pulse is getting thready.
你有没有尝试过插在她左支气管
Have you tried to intubate her left bronchus?
不行不行不行 没时间了 旋转
No, no, no. No time. Let's do a Texas twist.
-把气都推到左边去 -我知道
- Pushes all of the air to the left side. - Yeah, I know it.
不是这样
Not like this.
一看就知道是没上过战场的人
Only if you were in the battlefield.
打开紫外线光电子分光镜检查然后把手术刀给Clemens医生
Pick ups and scalpel to Dr. Clemens.
快点
Come on.
首先 切下近端肺韧带
First, you cut the inferior pulmonary ligaments proximally.
好 切完了
Okay, done.
现在转门
Rotating the hilum now.
看到了么 再快一点
See? A little faster.
我会把它缝起来的
I'll suture it down.
氧气增加到百分之92
Oxygen's up to 92%.
好的
Okay.
血压上升到114/70
New B.P.'s 114/70.
他妈的 德克萨斯式旋转
Son of a bitch. Texas twist.
做的不错 你们俩
Nice job...both of you.
她必须要进手术室
We gotta get her to the OR
我来好了
I got it from here.
我说了 让我来
I said, I got it from here.
-她需要一名外科医生  -我知道了
- She needs a surgeon. - I heard you.
但她是我的病人
But she's my patient.
她不是你的病人
She's not your patient.
在急诊室你把她病情稳定下来 的确做得不错
You did a great job of stabilizing her in the E.R.,
不过她现在需要手术 我要把她带上楼
but she needs surgery now. I'm taking her upstairs.
我要一起去
And I'm going with you.
我们这里不这么办事
We do things differently around here.
他是对所有人都那么屌 还是只针对我
Is he a dick to everyone or just me?
他 对他的病人非常负责
Well, he's very passionate about his patients.
是啊 我也很负责 但我可没那么屌
Yeah, so am I, but I'm not a dick.
不过我还是要说
I gotta say, though.
这夜班可真碉堡
This night shift's pretty baller.
不过我喜欢
I like getting out.
嘿 Chulita
Hey, Chulita.
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
你们俩原来认识
You two know each other?
岂止是认识
I know her real well.
我是她爸
I'm her daddy.
刀没切到动脉 真是幸运
He's very lucky that the knife didn't hit an artery.
早知道该让他出点血
Too bad he didn't bleed out.
哟 小姑娘现在还挺有脾气
Well, she got a temper, huh?
我女儿在这儿工作多久了
How long my little girl been working here?
这工作肯定给的钱很多吧 不是么
Money must be -- must be makin' bank, no?
干这行的一般都赚多少钱
What's a job like this pay anyway?
就估计一下  大概多少钱呢
Just, you know, ball -- ballpark?
宝贝儿 你怎么看
What do you think, sweetie?
你叫什么
You got a name?
好吧 你知道么 现在搭讪有点不合时宜
Okay, you know what? You're being really inappropriate.
现在请你保持安静 可以吗
I'd appreciate it if you would stop talk--
宝贝儿 现在不方便
It's not a good time, honey.
我不知道我们在哪儿 我们
I don't know where we are. We --
-我们好像 好像在 路中央 我也不知道什么地方    -什么
- We're in, like, in the middle of the road somewhere, - What?
-我把车开到停车区           -别慌 说慢点
- and I pulled off the freeway... - Hold...shh... slow down.
慢点讲 我 我听不清
Slow down! I-I can't hear you.
Topher 嗯 Lynn和我还好 不过我们
Topher, uh, uh, Lynn and I are okay, but we're...
你 你是说
What do you...what do you...
你说的到底什么意思 我不懂你什么意思
What do you mean...what do you mean,
你是遭遇车祸了吗
you kind of got in an accident?
我能回来的话一定回来
I'll be back when I can!
我 我需要一辆救护车
And I-I need an ambulance!
他们被倒下的大树截断了去路
They're blocked in the bay by the fallen trees.
你不能去 我们这儿正缺人手
You can't go! We're shorthanded!
我老婆被卡在路边正临盆
My wife is in labor on the side of a road...
她肚子里怀了双胞胎 我要走了
having twins. I'm leaving.
通往Willow City的路已经被完全堵死
The roads in Willow City have been shut down completely...
抱歉 大伙儿 要省电了
Sorry, folks. Power conservation.
情况很好 谢谢
This is good. Thank you.
嘿 T.X.U那儿进展如何
Hey, anything from T.X.U.?
他们现在连中转站都没弄好
They haven't even started working on the transmission station.
但是如果圣安东尼奥市那边没有人过来的话
But we have enough fuel if the rest of San Antonio
我们就有足够的油去圣安东尼奥
doesn't show up tonight.
不过我们需要Topher  TC在哪里
But we need Topher back. And where is T.C.?
他在手术室 Heather 你有没有
Well, he was in the OR Hey, Heather, did you...
我告诉过TC你需要他
I told T.C. That you needed him,
-但他还在那里   -好吧，我去找他
- but he's still in there. - All right, I'll get him.
-嘿 有人能让Dew把那人给拖过来么  -我来
- Hey, can somebody get Drew to take this man, please? - On it.
Landry 你能负责以下药品剂量吗
Hey, Landry, can you do some medical intake?
要等我忙完神经科那边
As soon as I get back from the psych floor.
你们会好起来的
You all are healed!
多谢 好 各位
Thanks. All right, everybody.
我们需要快点工作起来
We need to get the walking
先把受伤的人安排在等候间验伤
wounded into the waiting room for triage.
我们没地儿了。
We're running out of space here.
呃 德拉克鲁兹医生
Uh, Dr. De la Cruz?
你爹似乎赖着不走
Your dad's kind of not leaving.
他一直在说他想见你
He keeps asking for you.
好吧
Okay.
我来了
I'm coming!
堵车了 我正在找你
The road is blocked. I'm trying to find you.
别挂电话！
Just hang on!
上次你分娩了12个小时
Last time, your labor took 12 hours.
所以这次放轻松 亲爱的
So just relax, baby.
快点来
Get in here faster.
你能让林恩听电话吗
Can you put Lynn on?
是我 -老爸 你在哪儿
- Here. - Dad, where are you?
情况变得越来越奇怪了
It's getting really weird in here.
我 我就快到了
Yeah, I'm...I'm close. I'm almost there. Just give your mom
给你妈一块毛巾或者T恤衫让她咬在嘴里
a towel or t-shirt to bite on.
你现在就得过来
You need to get here now!
现在 把你的手伸进你妈妈的阴道里
Now, what I need you to do is reach into your mom's vagina
然后告诉我宫口是否正在打开。
and tell me if her cervix is starting to open.
用 用啥
With -- with what?
给你的手指消消毒 宝贝儿
Just Purell your finger, honey.
加油 我知道你能行的
Come on! I know you can do it.
你在检查么
Are you checking?
似乎 似乎是的
I think so.
摸上去有点 有点黏糊糊的
It's...it...it's squishy,
像香蕉 或者燕麦
Like a banana or oatmeal.
你能告诉我宫口有没有打开吗
Okay, can you tell me if it's starting to open?
我不太确定 摸到的一切东西都太湿了
Not really. Everything's just too wet.
湿 有多湿
Wet? How wet?
整个车座都被浸湿了 -噢 上帝啊 你们在哪里
- The whole seat is soaked. - Oh, God. Where are you?
按喇叭 按响喇叭
Honk the horn! Honk the horn!
老天哪 那个色眯眯的甘道夫又来了
Oh, God, here comes Gandalf the horny.
有啥大不了的
What's the big deal?
你要拍啥片他都会随你摆布
He'll give you all the X-rays you ever need.
我看你干脆跟他约个会得了
Just go out with him once.
那我看你也去跟茉莉的侄女约个会得了
You go out with Mollie's niece.
呵呵 但我不敢啊 我怕莫莉得寸进尺
Yeah, uh...I can't. She'll be on me even more.
她会问我 你喜欢她吗
She'll be like, "Did you like her?"
你会再约她吗
"Are you gonna call her again?"
-别想这个了 我不能... -你最好想出点儿法子来
- Forget that. I can't... - You gotta figure out something,
因为她正在向这儿大步迈进 并且似乎心意已决
'cause she's coming over here and she looks determined.
-啥 别啊 -德鲁
- What? No. - Drew!
我侄女特蕾西打电话找你
I got my niece Tracy on the line.
-亲我 快点亲我 -你是啥…
- Just kiss me. Kiss me. - What do you...
好了 问题解决了
All right. Problem solved.
行了 我们开始吧
All right, here we go.
里面比外面好些 没那么疯狂
It's a little less crazy inside here.
另外 我还给你的伤口找了个特别的创可贴
Also, I found a very special band-aid for your scratch.
我造它很炫酷
I know it's impressive.
来吧
Here we go.
好了 我看一下
All right, let's see.
瞧 行了
Voilà. There we go.
我想见见妈咪
I wanna see my mommy.
我知道你想 但是...
I know you do, bud. But, uh...
医生们还在楼上为她治疗呢 好吗
The doctors are still upstairs fixing her up. Okay?
嗯 先穿暖和点 好吗
Hey, let's, uh, let's get you warm, yeah?
好吧
Okay.
我能跟你呆在一起吗
Can I stay with you?
呃  似乎  似乎不行
Uh, not -- not really.
因为我还有其他病人
Um, because I have some other patients
他们都等着我呢 所以我...
that I have to help out first. Okay? So I'll...
噢噢 嘿 不 别这样
Oh. Oh. Hey. No, no, no.
别   别哭好么 嗯...
Don't...don't do that. Um...
你可以跟我在一起 没问题
You can definitely stay with me.
好么 其实我 嗯 还要你来帮我忙呢
Okay? Because I-I actually need your help.
呃 我得给病人们贴标签
Um...I have these tags that I have to put on some patients.
让医生知道治疗的优先级
Tells the doctors who they should treat first.
我想 你能帮上忙
Think you can maybe help me with that?
行吗 那好
Yeah? Okay.
嗯 走吧 我们过去
Uh, let's go get 'em. Let's go get 'em.
真有趣
Interesting.
我从来没在这样的医院工作过
I've never worked at a hospital
急诊医生竟然和外科医生一起做手术
where the E.R. Docs operate alongside surgeons.
是吗 那你该见见世面了
Yeah? Well, maybe you'll learn something new.
说实话 我已经受益匪浅了
Well, actually, I'm learning a lot.
很好
Good.
TC  十分钟前我就让希瑟上来叫你了
T.C., I sent Heather up here ten minutes ago to get you.
楼下主治医生相当紧缺
We are seriously short on attendings downstairs.
-注意有出血 -对 把4-0羊肠线给我
- Watch that bleeder. - Yeah, 4-oh silk to me.
我来缝合
I'll tie it off.
TC
Tc t.C.
我知道你很看重你手中的病人
I know your patients mean a lot to you,
但我一个人应付得来  真的
but I've got this. Seriously.
急诊室迫切需要你
And I need you in the E.R.
托佛的妻子半路上开始阵痛了
Topher's wife went into labor somewhere on the side of the road,
十分钟前他去找她了
and he took off about 10 minutes ago to get her.
-他有说地点吗 -没有
- Did he say where? - No.
拿着
Take that.
T 你不能走
Tee, you can't go. All right?
我也不想这样
I don't like this situation either,
但就像我说的 我们现在紧缺主治医生
but like I said, we are seriously short on attendings.
需要的时候呼叫我
Page me if you need me.
我不会的
I won't.
准备闭合
Set me up to close.
妈的 打不通
Damn it. It's not going through.
信号塔可能超负荷了
The towers are probably overloaded.
听着 托佛和珍妮特会没事的
Look, Topher and Janet will be okay.
她上次分娩花了12个小时
Her labor took 12 hours the last time,
所以 她还是有希望在破羊水之前赶到的
so... hopefully she'll be back before her water even breaks.
楼下急诊真的需要你
And we need you downstairs.
好吧
Yeah. Okay.
斯科特是个优秀的外科医生
Scott is an excellent surgeon.
是啊 他很厉害 我只是不喜欢
Yeah, he's good. I just don't like
别人对你指手画脚
Anybody telling you what to do?
谁喜欢被指挥了 但是总有秩序等级
Who does? But there's a pecking order,
如果他来这里 你就该学学怎么合作
and if he comes here, you will have to learn to work together.
"如果"  他会来这里吗
"If" -- "If" He comes?
我们还没做最后决定
We haven't decided yet.
-呃 好吧 好吧 当然 -什么
- Uh-huh. Okay, okay, sure. - What?
噢 只是 呃
Oh, it's just, uh...
拉戈萨希望他来 史考特似乎也想来
Ragosa wants him here. Scott seems to wanna be here.
只是 额 我只是想知道他还在等什么
Just, uh, just wondering what the holdup is.
赶紧接待病人 我们得去帮忙了
Grab a patient. We're getting backed up.
好了 厄尼 你应该稍微吃点东西
Okay. Ernie, uh, you should probably eat a little something,
即便是这种垃圾食品
even if it's this crap.
呃 你还可以玩玩我的手机
Um...You can also play with my phone.
我每隔二十分钟就过来看你
I will check on you every 20 minutes,
我隔20分钟就来给你检查一次
我会回来的 好吗
but I gotta get back, okay?
好了 来击个掌
So...Hey, up high.
这 这是怎么了
What -- what is it?
我的肩膀好痛
My shoulder hurts.
真奇怪 你肩膀之前没那么脆弱吧
That's weird. It wasn't tender before, right?
好了 来 让我们看看
Okay, uh, let's see.
也没有擦伤或者别的什么啊
There's no bruising or anything. Um...
只是你背上有个小小的伤口而已
Just that... itty bitty cut on your back.
你不能总是给人添麻烦
You cannot keep bothering people.
有三个护士分别来跟我讲
I've had three different nurses tell me
-说你正在找我 -看来这么做的确有用
- that you're looking for me. - Well... it worked.
这儿是医院
This is a hospital.
在这里 人们必须努力工作来救助其他人
People have jobs to do so that other people don't die,
而今晚这里格外的人满为患
and tonight is more swamped than most nights,
所以我给你一分钟 把你要说的说明白
so you have one minute to say what you need to say,
然后你就得离开
and then you gotta leave.
我真不欣赏你这种态度 我的女儿
Not loving the attitude, Mija.
我非常反感你这种态度 说真的
Not loving the attitude at all.
我还清楚 你只是想要钱而已
And I know that you just want money,
好吧 你还有50秒
so now you have 50 seconds.
别跟我这么讲话
Don't talk to me like that.
你要多少钱
How much do you need?
直说吧
Just say it.
五千
5k.
你在逗我吗
What?
我跟不好的人搅合到一块儿去了
I got in with the wrong pple.
你永远跟不好的人搅合在一块儿
You're always with the wrong people.
我可没这么多钱
I don't have it.
而且 就算我有 我也不会给你的
And even if I did have it, I wouldn't give it to you.
我跟你没关系了
I'm done with you.
我是你的家人 你怎么能和我没关系
You are never done with your family.
我不是说和我的家人没关系
I didn't say I was done with my family.
我是说你 所以马上离开这儿
I said I was done with you. Now leave.
是啊 看看你 你那些厉害的朋友们
Yeah. Look at you, all your fancy friends
看着我时就好像在看什么脏东西
giving me the stink eye.
一群来自北方的势利眼
Bunch of snobs from the north side --
就是这样
That's all that is.
而你 丢下了我
And to think of you abandoning me
就是为了那群人
for the likes of that!
我丢下你
Me abandon you?
我为了走到今天 拥有这一切 曾经累得半死不活
I have worked like an animal for everything that I have,
而你呢 除了麻烦什么也没给我
and I never got anything but grief from you.
你把我的整个童年都给毁了
You wrecked my childhood.
你偷我的钱
You stole my money.
你根本就是把我的人生都给毁了
You completely screwed up my life!
很久 很久以前 你就丢下我了
You abandoned me a long, long time ago.
兰德里 我 我需要这笔钱
Landry, I-I need the money!
你们没听到我说的吗 还是我每句话都得说两遍
Did anybody miss anything, or do I need to repeat it?
没有吧 好的
No? Good.
呃 嗨 你好 你是徳韦恩吧
Uh, hey, hey there. Dwayne, right?
你会帮我这个小忙的吧
Do me a solid, would you?
这个小朋友要做个CT 很快就好
This little dude needs a C.T. Scan kinda quick.
新人 这可不是它快不快的问题 排最后面去
Not how it works, new guy. Back of the line.
好吧 问题是
See, the thing is,
厄尼 呃 就是那个家伙
Ernie, um -- that's his name --
可能有左肩部放射痛
may have a positive Kehr sign.
呃 隔膜受到
Um, irritation of the diaphragm
来自腹腔内血液的刺激
from intra-abdominal blood,
导致了间接的肩膀疼痛
causing referred shoulder pain.
喔 听起来真高大上啊 医生
Wow. Lot of big words, doc.
我说过了 排到最后去
Like I said, back of the line.
听明白了吗
You dig?
我来翻译一下吧 科技白痴
Let me translate, tech dork.
这个孩子今晚失去了他的家
This little kid just lost his home tonight.
他的妈妈在楼上 正生命垂危
His mom is upstairs circling the drain,
而他很可能会体内大出血
and he might be hemorrhaging internally.
所以他可能会死
So he could die.
现在你明白了吗
Now do you dig?
我大腿内侧有颗痣 我想把它除掉
I've got a mole on my inner thigh I want removed.
如果你答应我把它搞掉 你就可以排最前面来
Promise to get rid of it, you go to the front of the line.
你不按我说的做 我就把它剐下来
Just do it, or I will rip it off.
爸爸 它要出来了
Dad! It's coming.
我能看到它的头
I can see its head!
哦 这不是我们牛逼哄哄的医生吗
Oh. There he is, cock of the walk.
你最好解释一下为什么你没有打电话给我的侄女
Knew there was a reason why you wouldn't call my niece.
呃 那是因为 我
Uh, that's -- I'm...
对不起 我想 我应该说些什么的
sorry. I guess... I should've said something.
你真无耻 你们臭男人都无耻
You're a dog. All men are dogs.
但是我喜欢克里丝塔
But I like Krista.
所以你最好别把这事儿搞砸
So you better not mess this up.
我盯着你呢 伙计
I got my eye on you, buster.
好的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
刚才有人呼我吗
Just got paged.
圣安东尼奥警署送来一个在便利店发现的裸男
S.A.P.D. Brought in a naked guy they found at Circle K.
由于他重度病残 他们安置了一个支架
They placed a hold for grave disability.
嗨 肯尼
Hey, Kenny.
你能把那个穿长袍的人带到3号床位吗
Can you bring toga man and put him in curtain 3?
没问题 医生
Sure thing, doc.
谢谢
Thanks.
你 你还好吗
You -- you okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
好的 我看到你父亲还在这儿呢
Okay. I see your dad's still here.
是啊 他就想让我不舒服
Yeah, he likes to make me uncomfortable.
-你希望我把他赶出去吗 -不不 没事儿
- You want me to throw him out of here? - No, it's fine.
反正他还是会回来的
He'll just keeping coming back.
好吧 你关心我 我很感激
Look, I appreciate the concern,
只是要解释清楚实在是太复杂了
but this is just way too involved
还会把你卷进来
and complicated to explain.
我只是想帮帮你
I'm just trying to help.
我知道 我知道你想帮我 但是
I know. It's what you do, but...
平心而论 我和你的关系
you and I really don't have the type of relationship
还没到谈论这事的地步
where we talk about things.
对吧
Do we?
那并不意味着我们不能谈论这件事
That doesn't mean we still can't talk about things.
我的意思是 我可以
I mean, I can --
听着 我 我一直在考虑
Look, I -- I've been thinking,
虽然我并不知道你和乔丹之间到底发生了什么
and I don't know what's going on with you and Jordan,
但我想你自己
and I don't think either of you
也并不清楚你和乔丹之间到底发生了什么
know what's going on with you and Jordan,
我只知道
but I just know that
我不想再夹在你们两人之间了
I don't wanna be in the middle of it anymore.
我和乔丹之间什么也没有
There is nothing with me and Jordan.
兄弟 你是一个
Dude, you guys are the poster children
不会处理感情问题的好男人
of unresolved feelings,
可是我不想成为你的备胎
and I'm not really into being plan "B,"
所以 我想我们还是做朋友吧
so...let's just be friends.
谢谢你一直以来对我的帮助
And thank you for offering to help,
我会照顾好自己的
but I'm used to handling things on my own.
呃 如果你还想再谈谈的话 我会
If you, uh, if you still wanna talk about anything, I'm...
Tc t.C.
保罗在放射科等你 那个孩子出事了
Paul needs you in radiology. It's the kid.
发生什么事了
What happened?
他说他肩膀有点疼
He was complaining of referred shoulder pain,
我就给他安排了个CT扫描  但是他没有脉搏了
so I ordered a C.A.T. Scan, but he lost his pulse.
马上给他进行心肺复苏
Hold C.P.R. A minute.
我得看看他心电图的基本走势
I need to see his underlying rhythm.
正弦波 糟糕
Sine wave, damn it.
他的钾含量过高
His potassium's sky high.
好像有一小块弹片
It looks like a tiny piece of shrapnel
从他的肋骨穿过
transected the kid's ureter.
把他的尿管切断了
From that cut on his ribs.
肾外伤会直接导致肾衰竭
The kidney trauma must have put him into renal failure.
这也是他体内的钾如此高的原因了
Which explains the elevated potassium.
不错 他需要氯化钠
All right, he needs an amp of calcium chloride,
碳酸钠和10单位的胰岛素
sodium bicarb, and 10 units of insulin.
很好 保罗 不错
Good, Paul. That's good.
好了 德维恩
All right, Dwayne,
马上准备肾脏透析
page nephrology for emergency dialysis.
我已经在电话通知了
Calling now.
药效来了 心律正常
Meds are in. Rhythm's stabilizing.
他有脉搏了吗 嗯 很好
And he's got a pulse? Okay, that's good.
是不是说他会没事的
Does that mean he's gonna be all right?
药物暂时起了作用
The meds are a quick fix.
钾含量还是很高
Potassium's still sky high.
保罗 带上扫描 我们走
Paul, grab that scan. Let's go.
他得尽快做透析
He needs dialysis, asap.
亲爱的 加油
Come on, baby!
再用力推一次 我知道你能行的
Just one more push! I know you got it in you!
加油 用劲
Come on! Dig deep!
使劲 妈妈 使劲
Push, mom, push!
就是这样 带着工具么
That's it! You got the kit?
很好
Yes...
我们有了
We have...
一个小女娃娃
a baby girl!
谢天谢地
My greatest...
她还好么
Is she okay?
嗯 她很漂亮
Yes. She's so beautiful.
我们得剪一下脐带
We gotta cut the umbilical cord.
给我钳子和剪子
Get the clamps and scissors.
夹在这里和那里 把中间剪断
Just clamp here and here, and cut in between.
看看你的杰作
Look what you did.
Look what you made.
瞧瞧你的小妹妹
Look at your little sister.
是你的小妹妹 把你的外套拿来
It's your sister. Grab your hoodie,
让我们用干净的东西把她裹起来
And let's wrap her in something clean.
是你的小妹妹啊
It's your sister.
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my gosh.
你准备好再来一次了吗
You ready for round two?
你有手电筒吗
You got the flashlight?
爸爸 那是什么
Daddy, what is that?
什么
What is it?
出什么事了
What's wrong?
没事 恩 那是 恩 孩子的脚
Nothing. It's a -- it's a foot.
- 什么 - 大家要保持冷静
- A what? - Everybody just stay calm.
我马上来解决
I'm just gonna reach in there
我把小姑娘翻个面给你
and turn this little girl around.
抱着孩子
Hold the baby.
我们需要去医院
We need to get to the hospital.
胎儿胎位不正 不能顺产了
Baby's in breech. It can't be born like this.
那我应该怎么做
What should I do?
你要从我兜里翻出手机
I need you to reach into my pocket, grab my phone.
跑到有信号的地方
Run around until you find a signal.
911 可能很忙碌
9-1-1 is probably overwhelmed.
你要打给 T C叔叔
I need you to call Uncle T.C.
告诉他我需要他的帮助
Tell him I need him right now.
- 快 快跑 -好的
- Go, go. - Okay.
- 不 -有我陪着你
- No. - Just stay with me.
你让她去哪了
No. Where did you -- where did you send her?
- 呆在这 呆在这 -出什么事了
- Stay with me. Stay with me. - What's wrong?
没什么事儿
Nothing is wrong.
你得告诉我哪儿有问题
You have to tell me what's wrong.
你做得很好
That was a good catch.
如果你没有做扫描检查的话
We'd be 10 steps behind if you hadn't --
我们可能就救不了他了
hadn't got the scan.
很棒 很及时
Good call.
啊 幸亏他没事 他是很棒的小孩
Yeah. Um, just glad he's okay. He's a really cool little guy.
是啊 你对孩子有一套
You have a way with kids, you know.
你 有没有 想过
You, uh, you ever think about doing a fellowship
去儿科急诊室干干呢
in E.R. Pediatrics?
嗯 没有 从来没有 那 那不适合我
Uh, no, never. That is   that is not for me.
为什么
Why?
嗯 我来自一个外科医生世家
Uh, well, I come from a family of surgeons.
你知道 我的爷爷 我的父亲
You know, my grandfather, my father
我父亲的两个兄弟 我的两个兄弟都是外科医生
both his brothers, both my brothers.
你知道 家族传统 我必须做一个急诊室医生 所以
You know, being an E.R. Doc is already pushing it, so...
呃 而且 那真的不适合我
Uh, I'm just   that's not for me.
我不知道 只是 嗯 如果你有这个天赋
I don't know. It just, um, if you have a gift,
你知道 就考虑一下吧
just, you know... think about it.
我真的很抱歉 你今天过得如此糟糕
I'm really sorry you had such a crappy day today.
但是我 我保证
But I-I promise,
从现在起一切都会好起来的
everything is gonna be awesome from here on out.
没事的 大家
It's okay, everybody!
这种事情曾经发生过
This has happened before.
发电机几秒之后就会重新开始工作
The generators will kick on again in just a few seconds.
好吧 这次不是开玩笑的 我们断电了
Okay, this is not a drill. We are out of power.
请大家看好你的病人
Everybody, keep manually bagging your patients.
我们不知道断电会持续多久
We don't know how long this is gonna last.
拉戈萨,发生了什么事?
Ragosa, what happened?
我不是有有足够的燃料么
I thought we had enough fuel.
是的 但该死的发电机因为暴风雨被淹了
We do. Damn generators flooded because of the storm.
我们早就想把它搬楼上的
We were gonna move 'em upstairs,
但一直推到了现在也没搬
but we never got to it.
正在维修 但需要一段时间
Maintenance is working on it, but it'll take a while.
T.C. 我们正在关闭后挡板和食品卡车的
T.C., we're running power off the mini gennies
迷你型发电机
from the tailgate and food trucks.
太好了 让尽可能把电力转向手术室
Great. Run cable to as many trauma rooms as possible.
关掉出口标志灯 用电池灯代替
Take off the exit signs and use their battery lights.
在这样的情况下 我们不能营业
We can't stay open under these conditions.
整个一楼都没电了
The entire first floor is out.
救护车必须改道去另一家医院
We have to reroute the ambulances to another hospital.
我们不能关门
We can't close.
救护车可以去别的医院
You can reroute the new traffic,
但是这儿的病人怎么办呢
but what about the people who are here?
而且一直有病人过来
And people are still coming in.
如果我们不做这些 会有人死的
If we don't do this, people are gonna die.
我们必须尽我们所能 好吗
We have to do what we can, okay?
好吧
Okay.
好吧 街的对面有一个建筑工地
All right, there's a construction site across the street.
我会派一些员工去借他们的灯
I'll send some staffers over to get some of their lights.
我打电话让我单位的人去
I'll call the guys in my unit for that.
他们大概十分钟后到
They can be here in 10 minutes.
好 好 T.C. 做你该做的
Okay, okay, T .C., just do what you gotta do.
我会处理新病人
I'll take any new cases.
啊 我现在真的需要一个护士
Man, I could really use a nurse right now.
迈克尔可以做护士嗷 他受过一些培训
Michael can jump in. He's got some training.
告诉我需要做什么
Just tell me what to do.
-托佛 终于 -T.C.叔叔
- Topher, finally   - Uncle T.C.,
能听到吗 我只有一格信号
Can you hear me? I only have one bar,
-我妈妈刚生了一个孩子 —好的 好的 好的
- and my mom just had a baby! - Okay, okay, okay.
我来说你来做
Here's what I need you to do.
-看看你的电话 -T.C. 我需要你
- Look at your phone... - T.C., I need
打开GPS定位 告诉我你的确切位置
Open the G.P.S. And give me your exact location.
对的
Right.
是距离79英里的标记
It's mile marker 79.
—我真的好害怕 —坚持到底 亲爱的
- I'm really scared! - Hang tough, sweetie.
—我来解决这个问题 —厄尼的透析机断电了
- I'm gonna fix this. - Ernie's dialysis is down.
我就知道会这样 好吧 我有个主意 我们走吧
I figured it would be. Okay. I got another idea. Let's go.
嗨 是T.C. 我知道断电是真的
Hey, it's T.C. I know there's no games.
我没有跟谁打赌 听着 我需要你极力配合
I'm not betting. Listen, I need a gigantic favor.
靠这些小型发电机维持不了那么久
We don't have that long on those small gennies,
所以我想到了另外的方法
so I've got another solution.
我们要去旧的学校
We're gonna go old school.
去任何学校都行 他的移植器官在南边的某个地方
I will take any school. His vitals are going south,
QRS波也再次变宽
and his QRS is widening again.
我又注射了1单位的钙,但不起作用
I pushed another amp of calcium, but it's not working.
没关系,会好起来的 我们要做腹膜透析
All right, we'll be fine. We're gonna do peritoneal dialysis.
嘿 给我梯子 快点
Hey! Give me the ladder, right now.
我们不需要等待来电 我见过很多地方这样做过
Don't need any power. They do it a lot in places
以应对无法透析的状况
where they don't have access to hemodialysis.
好的
Okay.
把这些灯放在他的腹部
Put these lights on his belly.
我感觉好奇怪啊
I feel weird.
这是因为你的身体没有正常运转
That's because your body's not doing its job right.
我们要在你胃里放一种特殊的药物
We're gonna put a special medicine
来吸出所有坏东西
inside your stomach to suck out all the bad stuff.
我们先把管子放进肚子里 好吗
We just need to put a tube inside your tummy first, okay?
-好的 -好
- Okay. - Okay.
你要跟我呆一起,保罗?
You're gonna stay with me, Paul?
你最好相信
You better believe it.
我哪儿也不去 好吗
I'm not going anywhere, okay?
好了 开始了
Here. Come on.
好吧 伙计们 把这些灯弄亮
All right, let's get these lights up, guys.
好 让他们对着手术室
All right, point them towards the trauma rooms.
嘿 各位 让我们给肯尼和
Hey, everybody, let's give a big hand
陆军预备役作战支援队鼓掌
to Kenny and the army reserve combat support team.
谢谢 小伙子们
Thank you, boys.
好 太棒了
Okay, it's good.
好 将它收紧
Okay, wrap it tighter.
你需要压着来止血
You need the pressure to stop the bleeding.
像这样
Like this?
没错 做得很好
Exactly. You got a nice touch.
告诉我你是否越来越感到想吐
Just let me know if you're getting queasy.
嘿 克里丝塔 那边情况怎么样
Hey, Krista, how are we doing over there?
都在控制当中
All under control.
-兰德里  -一切都好
- Landry? - All good.
从医学院毕业后还没有给人缝过针
Haven't stitched anyone up since med school.
希望我没有落东西在她身体里
Hope I didn't leave anything inside her.
嘿 听着
Hey, listen.
我知道情况很混乱 但是
I know things have been crazy, but...
如果你父亲的事需要帮忙
if you need help with the whole dad thing --
没事的 我能解决
Oh. It's under control.
-马上就好 先走一步 -嗯
- It will be. Excuse me. - Sure.
所以说 TC在这儿跟大家相处得怎么样啊
So how does T.C. Treat everybody on this shift?
很好啊
Great.
虽然他脾气暴躁了点 但本质还好
He's intense, but he's a good guy.
他和乔丹很默契
He and Jordan make a good team.
哦 糟了
Oh, damn it.
上腔静脉阻塞扩散到了右心房
The S.V.C. Tear extends into the right atrium.
抽吸
Suction.
谁去联系一下TC  我一双手完全不够用
Someone get T.C. I need a second pair of hands.
血管钳
Clamp.
我这儿有500刀 要多了也没有
I got $500. It's the best I can do.
拿着钱离开这儿
Now take it and get out of here.
500刀不够用
$500 ain't gonna do it.
我之前 不敢和你说
I-I didn't wanna upset you before,
但如果我不还他们钱的话
but if I don't get them their money...
他们会报复到你妈妈头上
they're gonna take it out on your ma.
我才不信你的鬼话
I don't believe you.
他们威胁我了
They made threats,
你知道 那些人不随便开玩笑的
and these people don't play games.
我知道
I know them.
我需要5千刀
I need 5 grand.
我说了 我没有
I told you. I don't have it.
丫头 看你身上穿的衣服 我就知道你肯定有的
Baby, the clothes you're wearing tell me you do.
我真没有
I don't have it
我还欠着医学院20万
because I'm 200 grand in debt from medical school.
我还要支付茱莉亚和汤米的学费
I pay for Julia and Tommy's private school,
这些本该是你来承担的
which you should be doing.
所以 别来跟我讨论
So don't talk to me about what I have
我有没有钱的问题
and I don't have.
好吧 我错了 我是个混蛋
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm a jerk.
但是 如果你真的爱你妈妈
But if you love your mama at all,
你会想方设法给我5千的
you'll get me the $5,000.
我在候诊室等你
And I'll be in the waiting room, waiting.
怎么了
What happened?
上腔静脉阻塞已经到了心房后壁
The S.V.C. Tear has posterior atrial involvement.
我用了心肺分流术来弥补
I've used the heart-lung bypass to make the repair,
可是强度还不够
but there's not enough power.
血压降到60
Pressure's down 60.
如果你有什么战地医疗术
If you've got any battlefield medicine
可行的话 就跟我讲讲吧
you think might work, I'd love to hear it.
如果没有的话 她会死的
If not, she's going to die.
所以说 是真的吗
So it's true?
妈 你不能一直任由他搞出这些破事来
Mom. You can't keep letting him pull this crap.
我真希望你离开他
I wish you would leave him.
妈
Mom...
我知道你很害怕 但一切都会好起来的
I know you're scared. It's gonna be okay.
去提提那儿 好吗
Just go to Titi's, okay?
我会想办法的
I'll figure it out.
我爱你
I love you.
兰德里
Landry.
我真的要谢谢你的激将
Man, I really gotta thank you for the push.
能亲手为一个患者做手术真是
Actually working on a patient --
你根本无法想象 我刚刚做了什么
You would not believe what I just did.
真是不可思议
It was incredible.
不 喂 喂
No, whoa, whoa.
你怎么了
What's wrong?
没事
Nothing.
真的没事
Nothing?
拜托 关于我的一切我都告诉你了
Come on. I've told you everything about me.
到底怎么了
What's going on?
颈静脉-心房分流术
Jugulo-atrial shunt.
这还是我第一次亲历这种手术
It's the first one of those I've ever witnessed.
手术中维持静脉回流
Maintains venous return intraoperatively,
你知道的 这样就不需要人工心肺机了
So, you know, no heart-lung machine is needed.
真聪明啊你
Pretty clever, man.
在阿富汗的时候 这个法子帮了我好几次呢
Saved my ass a couple of times in Afghanistan.
谢谢你 TC
Thank you, T.C.
没事 职责所在
Hey. It's my job.
嗯 那个
Hey, man. Uh...
我应该告诉你
I should let you know
我即将上任
I'm going to take the job
成为新的创伤科主任
as the new head of trauma surgery.
很棒啊
Great.
为什么要告诉我
Some reason you're telling me?
嗯 因为这里会有所改变
Yeah, because things are going to change around here.
是吗
Is that right?
当然
Yes, that's right.
T 托佛打电话说 他还有五分钟就到了
Tee? Topher just called. He's five minutes away.
这是400刀 TC  现金
That's $400, T.C. Cash money.
-你居然让下注的人去 -他为了钱什么都做
- You sent your bookie? - He'll do anything for cash.
第一个婴儿顺利出来了
First one slid right out,
第二个则是正在足式臀位分娩 但脐带脱垂
Second's a footling breech with cord prolapse.
她必须马上产出
She has to come out now.
珍妮特 放松点 好吗
Just try and relax, Janet, okay?
又来电了 是个好兆头
The lights came back on. That's a good sign.
产科医生来电话了 他们换了条路
O.B. Just called. They rerouted her.
-她还有30分钟就到了 -坚持住
- She's still 30 minutes away. - Come on.
天 TC 她要生出来了
Son of a bitch. T.C., she wants to come out.
没事 没事 我们可以的
Okay, it's okay. We got this.
要出来了
It's coming!
不 不 我做不到
I can't... I can't... I can't...
没事的 亲爱的 你是最棒的
It's okay. You are my champion, baby.
太丢人了
This is so humiliating.
为什么 又不是你要这样的
Why? Because you asked for this crap?
我们都无法选择我们的家庭 兰德里
We don't get to choose our families, Landry.
我以后会报答你的 我发誓
I will pay you back, I swear.
我知道你会的
I know you will...
不然的话 我就扣你工资
Or else, I'll garner your wages.
开个玩笑啦
I'm kidding.
我只是
I'm just...
开个玩笑
I'm kidding.
嗯 说真的
No, uh, seriously,
你真的帮了我很多
you were a real big help to me.
所以能回报你我很开心
I'm happy to return the favor.
但是 我认为你是该和你父亲断绝来往了
But...I do think you need to cut ties with your dad.
和他断绝来往 就等于断绝和我妈妈的来往
I cut ties with him. I cut ties with my mom.
呃 我不
Well, I-I don't...
我不知道该说些什么
I don't know what to say other than
只是如果你需要和谁聊聊天的话
if you ever need someone to talk to,
我一直都在
uh, I'm around.
谢谢
Thank you.
之前从没有人为我做过这些
Nobody's ever done anything like this for me before.
恩 可能只是因为你
Well... maybe you've just been
总是和错的人在一块儿
hanging around with the wrong people.
身子出来了 但是头卡在子宫颈里了
The body's out, but the head is stuck in the cervix.
婴儿的心跳在减缓
The baby's heart is decelerating.
好的 乔丹 我有个注意 咱们试一试
Okay, Jordan, I have an idea. Let me try it.
我需要解剖剪
I need Mayo scissors.
TC
Tc t.C.
我发誓 如果你敢把你看到我 的事说出去 我
I swear, if you say one word about seeing my --
就再也不请我去吃晚饭了吗
Never get invited for dinner again?
那我可不想
I don't wanna blow that.
-帮我打开骨盆 -好的
- Help me open up the pelvis. - Okay.
-抬起她的腿 -好
- Let's lift her legs up. - Okay.
好
It's good.
我要做个子宫颈口切开术
I'm going to make a Duhrssen incision.
切开宫颈口应该能把头弄出来
Cutting the cervix should let the head come down.
好 保持呼吸 珍妮特  还有你  托佛
Okay, keep breathing, Janet. You, too, Topher.
一
One...
二 三
two, three.
使劲 使劲
Push. Push.
呼吸 用力 继续
Breathe and push. Breathe and push.
有作用了 你做得很好
It's working. You're doing so good.
她 她
Is -- is...
她出来了
And she's out.
你做到了
You did it. You did it!
她还好吗
Is she okay? Is she okay?
她很好
She's okay.
托佛
Toph.
托佛 她真漂亮
Toph...she is so beautiful.
嗨 我是你的TC叔叔
I'm your Uncle T.C. Hey.
你会说T叔叔吗
Can you say "Uncle T"? Huh?
谢谢你们帮忙
Oh, thank you for help us.
你好
Hello.
你好 我
Hello. Oh, my...
我爱你 兄弟
I love you, brother.
我也爱你 兄弟
Right back at you, buddy.
好啦
Oh. Okay.
嗨 厄尼
Hey, Ernie.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
现在你是个坚强的男子汉了 你知道吗
Now you're a pretty strong little guy. You know that?
我这是在哪
Where am I?
我把你移到了另一个房间
I, uh, I moved you to another room.
我不知道 我觉得你可能想要一个室友
I don't know. I figured you might want a roommate
之类的 所以
or something like that, so...
妈妈
Mommy!
我的儿子
There's my boy.
我以为你要死了
I thought you were gonna die.
以为我会离开你吗 孩子
And leave you, kiddo?
不会的
No way.
我差点就死了
I almost died.
什么
What?
是啊 这真是个波澜起伏的夜晚
Yeah, it was a... It was an interesting night.
一切的开始还是在你保护着你的儿子
Actually, it started when you protected your son
从风暴中脱险的时候 这真的很勇敢
from the storm, which was very brave.
而你 也很勇敢
You're brave as well.
导致13人死亡 这是近几十年来
13died, as a score injured in the worst storm
我们这里影响最大的风暴
we haven't seen this area for dacades...
嘿 亲爱的
Hi, honey.
今天过得怎么样
How was your day?
我收到了瑞克的短信
I got this text from Rick.
天哪 德鲁
Oh, my god, Drew.
他在回国的路上
He's coming home.
是啊 他活下来了 他要回家了
Yeah, he made it out of there. He's coming home.
他在阿富汗挺过来了
He survived Afghanistan.
给婴儿助产有点名堂 是吧
There is something about delivering a baby, huh?
我知道 它永远与时俱进
I know, right? It never gets old.
而且现在我可以和珍妮特说
Plus now I can tell Janet
我曾经把手伸进过她身体里 说她一辈子
I've had my hands inside her till the day she dies.
你怎么这么鬼畜
What is wrong with you?
嘿
Hey, uh...
你知道 斯科特要来了对吧
So, you know, Scott's coming here, right?
是 是啊 他确信通知了我
Yeah. Yeah, he made sure to tell me.
恩 听着
Yeah. Look...
我知道有些事会改变
I know it's gonna change things,
而且有一阵子会变得很奇怪
and I know it's gonna be weird for a while, but --
嘿 管它呢
Hey. Whatever, right?
嗯 嗯
No. No.
我想告诉你的是
What I'm trying to say to you
在过去的几个月
is that in the past few months
我和你共事的时候
that I've been working with you,
我觉得 我们又重新变成了朋友
I feel like...we're getting back to being friends again,
然后
and...
我挺喜欢的
I like that.
我觉得 我们一直都是朋友
I mean... we were always friends.
嗯
Well...
你一直都是我的朋友
You were always my friend.
我有段时间 在这儿并没做到最好
I wasn't the best there for a while.
不 Tee 你
No. Tee, you --
有些事情你掌控不了
You had some things that were beyond your control.
我还是
Still...
很抱歉
I'm sorry...
我把我们两人的关系搞砸了
That I messed things up... between us.
我也一样
Yeah Me, too.
没事的
Yeah, okay.
嘿 乔丹
Hey, Jordan --
斯科特在找你
Scott was looking for you.
哦 来了
Yeah, okay.
嘿 注意听 各位 注意听
Okay, listen up, everybody. Listen up.
我得感谢你们今晚的努力
I have to thank you guys for a great night.
你们出色地完成了工作 而现在
You did a bang-up job, but now...
我想向你们介绍
I'd like to introduce to you
创伤外科的新领导
the new head of trauma surgery --
斯科特 克里曼斯医生
Dr. Scott Clemens!
哦哦哦 看看这对儿
Whoo! Oh! Look at this.
我们要让这对舞会国王和王后
We have the prom king and queen power couple
来掌管这里了 给他们俩掌声
running this place. Give 'em a hand.
太好了
Yes!